successstory.com 2017-07-08

# Privacy Policy | SuccessStory

## Privacy Policy

### Successstory.com Online Privacy Statement

(The policies stated within this document are applicable to successstory.com on the World Wide Web.)

### Your Privacy Is Serious Business To Us!

The privacy of our visitors and members is very important to us. Since we do gather information about you, we provide this privacy statement to enable you to understand the terms and conditions associated with the collection of this data, as well as how we use it and how you can correct or change it. In addition, we make to you the following pledge:

### The Successstory.com Privacy Pledge

1\. Unless you otherwise agree (as indicated below), the information you give us or that we collect about you will not be shared with any third party, except with those third parties providing services to us ("our service providers") and then only in the form of statistical information which has been aggregated with other user information for the purposes of our own website research and development in an effort to better serve your needs.

2\. We will never contact you without your permission, and we will immediately terminate any communications with you upon request.

### Electronic Newsletters

You can choose to subscribe to one of our FREE electronic newsletters. These newsletters are distributed through our service provider. To subscribe, simply check the box for each newsletter you wish to receive, provide your e-mail address and zip code and then submit. From time-to-time, you may be asked to provide additional information such as job title, number of employees, country of origin, and type of business. As a subscriber to our newsletter, you also agree to receive advertisements, promotions, and special communications from Successstory. You can remove yourself from our newsletter e-mail lists by simply following the "Unsubscribe" directions included in each newsletter you receive or send an email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line to contact@successstory.com. Please be assured that the information you give us or that we collect about you in connection with your subscription to our electronic newsletters will not be shared with any third party, except with our service providers and then only in the form and for the purposes stated in the above Privacy Pledge.

### Franchise & Business Opportunity Lead Submission

The information, which you voluntarily provide in responding to those franchise and business opportunity advertisers conducting recruitment campaigns on our site ("lead information"), will only be shared with those specific franchise and/or business opportunity advertisers you have selected for the purpose of receiving additional information about them. Please be assured that, except for those franchise and/or business opportunity advertisers you have selected, the information you give us or that we collect about you in connection with this lead generation program will not be shared with any other third party, except with our service providers and then only in the form and for the purposes stated in the above Privacy Pledge.

### Expert Columnist Lead Submission

The information, which you voluntarily provide in responding to certain columnists on our site, will only be shared with those columnists you have selected for the purpose of receiving additional information about their products or services. Please be assured that, except for those columnists you have selected, the information you give us or that we collect about you in connection with this lead generation program will not be shared with any other third party, except with our service providers and then only in the form and for the purposes stated in the above Privacy Pledge.

### SuccessStory Assist Registration

The information you voluntarily provide in registering to access the SuccessStory Assist suite of interactive resources will only be shared with the named co-sponsor of this service, which may use such information to apprise you of its goods and/or services. Please be assured that, except for any co-sponsor of the SuccessStory Assist service, the information you give us or that we collect about you in connection with your registration for this service will not be shared with any third party, except with our service providers and then only in the form and for the purposes stated in the above Privacy Pledge.

### Usage Reports

In order to better understand traffic patterns of SucccessStory.com, we analyze our site activity to obtain overall usage statistics. These usage statistics provide us with certain information obtained through the use of cookies and from data within the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). Information we collect from the browser string includes domain name, browser type, operating system, geographic origin, referring domain and MIME type. Cookies allow us to track behavior on the site to determine content preferences and usage patterns. This information is for internal consumption and is only shared with third parties on a statistically aggregated basis. No specific or personally identifiable information collected through this process is ever shared with a third party.

### E-Mail Data Analysis

From time-to-time, we provide our e-mail lists (newsletters & special offers) to our service providers, which in turn provide us with specialized services, such as e-mail message deployment, merge-purge (identifying and removing duplicate addresses) of lists, statistical analysis and other data processing. Please be assured that the information you give us or that we collect about you in connection with your subscription to our electronic newsletters and/or special offers will not be shared with any third party, except with our service providers and then for the purposes stated in the above Privacy Pledge.

### Cookies

SuccessStory.com use cookies. A cookie is a small data file written to your hard drive. Cookies allow us to understand user behavior so we can more effectively develop information and programs to serve you better. Our third-party ad serving company, delivers a one-time cookie to your hard drive in order to better track ad impressions and click-through rates generated by your activity on our websites. Advertisers require information regarding ad impressions and click-through rates, and by providing them with this information, we are able to keep our websites free to our visitors. Please be assured that, except for sharing impressions and click-through rates with our third-party advertisers, the information you give us or that we collect about you in connection with our use of cookies will not be shared with any other third party, except with our service providers and then only in the form and for the purposes stated in the above Privacy Pledge.

If you're concerned about the use of cookies, you have the option to set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, or to turn off cookies entirely. The options to warn or disable cookies can be found in the "Options" or "Preferences" feature of your browser. You do not need to enable cookies in order to use SuccessStory.com

### Links to Other Sites

Please be aware that when you're on SuccessStory.com when you receive an e-mail message from us on behalf of a marketer according to permission granted through our opt-in process for newsletters and special offers, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control, such as the marketer's site. There may also be links to other sites from SuccessStory.com pages or from the e-mail message we send you that take you outside SuccessStory.com. These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.

### Third-Party E-Mail Collection

In addition to SuccessStory.com visitors providing permission to receive newsletters and special offers, we do work with various marketing partners to promote our newsletters and special offers to their visitors. Each promotion on third-party sites is branded under SuccessStory.com.

### Security

Protecting the security of your personal information is very important to us. When we store information you've provided to us, that information is protected by security measures that include "firewalls" (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps keep unauthorized visitors from accessing information within our computer network), "intrusion detection systems" (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps detect any unauthorized visitors), "secure socket layer" (data encryption used when transmitting certain information such as personal information from a form or a transaction within SuccessStory.com) and other security measures such as secure storage. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or data repository can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while SuccessStory.com strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.

### Reporting Unsolicited E-Mail

Despite our concerted efforts to prevent unsolicited (spam) e-mail relayed through SuccessStory.com servers, unsolicited e-mail may sometimes get through. SuccessStory.com NEVER sends unsolicited or spam e-mail. We view spam as a serious violation of privacy and a misuse of the internet in general. If you receive an unsolicited e-mail with a domain of SuccessStory.com, please send it immediately to contact@successstory.com. Upon receipt of the e-mail, we will do our utmost to track down the offender and take any actions necessary to stop spam messages.

### Correcting Information

You can correct or update any information you have provided to SuccessStory.com by following the instructions in any electronic newsletter or offering we send, or you may correct your information by sending an e-mail to contact@successstory.com .

### Deactivating

Any user receiving our electronic newsletter or who receives regular offers from our partners may opt out of our email list at any time by simply following the instructions to "Unsubscribe" within each newsletter or offering or send an an email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line to contact@successstory.com.

### Changes to the SuccessStory Privacy Policy

This privacy policy may be modified from time to time. If there is a significant change, we will indicate on our sites that our privacy policy has changed and provide a link to the new policy.

### Contacting SuccessStory

Should you have any questions, concerns or suggestions, you may contact SuccessStory.com by e-mail at contact@successstory.com
